const SportsData = [
    {
        question: "How many wards are there in Tokha Municipality?",
        options: ["12", "17", "7", "11"],
        correct: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the most used programming language?",
        options: ["Java", "Python", "C", "C++"],
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the prime minister of Nepal?",
        options: ["Ishor Pokherel", "Ram Shah", "Rajesh", "KP OLi"],
        correct: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What does HTML stands for?",
        options: ["Hyper Text MarkUp language", "High Teller Makes Language", "Hyper Tell Meet Late", "Hows The Mate Lies"],
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What year JavaScript launched ?",
        options: ["1996", "1990", "2019", "none of the above"],
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the first women to climb mount Everest?",
        options: ["Pasang Ale Sherpa", "Pasang Lhamu Sherpa", "Shree Lhamu sherpa", "Tenging Norgay Sherpa"],
        correct: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the richest person of Nepal?",
        options: ["Puspa kamal Dahal", "Baburam Bhatteri", "Bikash Chaudhary", "Binod Chaudhary"],
        correct: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the founder of Microsoft company?",
        options: ["Ali Baba", "Jack Ma", "Billgates", "Binod Chaudhary"],
        correct: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Where was Lord Buddha Born?",
        options: ["Lumbini", "Baudha", "Swaymbunath", "none of the above"],
        correct: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Birth place of Goddess Sita ?",
        options: ["Janakpur", "Rameshwor", "Harisiddhi", "Pokhara"],
        correct: 1,
    }
];

export default SportsData;